<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cisco ASA Woes</title>
      <link>/posts/untitled-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/untitled-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;cisco-asa-5510&#34;&gt;Cisco ASA 5510&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need to brush up on my networking skills, so I thought that I would dig out the old hardware that I purchased back when I initially got my CCNA certification. I figured I&amp;rsquo;d first start with this ASA Firewall since many job listing I have been seeing for Network Engineer jobs have mentioned firewall configuration.  I purchased this ASA in probably 2017 or 2018 and it was past end of life then (foreshadowing&amp;hellip;..).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;cisco-asa-5510&#34;&gt;Cisco ASA 5510&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need to brush up on my networking skills, so I thought that I would dig out the old hardware that I purchased back when I initially got my CCNA certification. I figured I&amp;rsquo;d first start with this ASA Firewall since many job listing I have been seeing for Network Engineer jobs have mentioned firewall configuration.  I purchased this ASA in probably 2017 or 2018 and it was past end of life then (foreshadowing&amp;hellip;..).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251205104321.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;configuration&#34;&gt;Configuration&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I plugged the ASA into power and connected a Cisco console cable to it, I ran the other end of the console cable through an RS232 to USB adapter and opened up PuTTY. After adjusting the serial settings I was able to easily get to the login prompt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;logging-in&#34;&gt;Logging In&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is where I hit my first snag, I had no idea what I set the username and password to 7 or 8 years ago&amp;hellip;. So I had to do a factory reset on the ASA which isn&amp;rsquo;t incredibly difficult but not something that is super intuitive. I had to interrupt the boot sequence and get into the ROM Monitor (ROMmon) mode and change the configuration register for the boot sequence telling it to ignore current config on the device. From there I was able to reboot it with no loaded config, delete the stored config and then start from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I assumed that this would be the hardest part&amp;hellip;..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251205105607.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;interface-setup&#34;&gt;Interface Setup&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From here, I set an IP address on one of the Ethernet ports and connected a laptop to that port. I setup the laptop on the same subnet and pinged the ASA successfully. I then enabled the http server on the ASA to enable access to the web GUI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251205105723.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;disaster-strikes&#34;&gt;Disaster Strikes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I attempted to visit the web GUI in my browser, only to be greeted with an SSL/TLS mismatch error&amp;hellip;. uh oh.  A quick web search revealed that this version of the ASA firmware only supports TLS 1.0 and the only fix is a firmware upgrade. Well that seems easy&amp;hellip;. except Cisco doesn&amp;rsquo;t just give out firmware files, and even if I still had an account with them that had access to updates, it would appear that they no longer have the files available for this ASA because it is soo old (eol was in 2018).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was about to give up, but remembered that I had a laptop that hasn&amp;rsquo;t been booted up in almost as long as this ASA and though maybe it might work to access the web GUI. I set that laptop up, attempted to access the web GUI in Chrome and received the same error. Then I realized that this laptop still had Internet Explorer on it. I tried in IE, it allowed me to load the page after choosing to ignore the certificate errors&amp;hellip;.. At this point I thought my problems were solved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The GUI for the ASA (Cisco ASDM) is a JAVA program, so the webpage loaded on the ASA is really just a download page for the JAVA file. I downloaded the file, but when I went to run it, the PC let me know that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have JAVA installed&amp;hellip; ok fine, so I installed Java and tried again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest version of Java doesn&amp;rsquo;t support the ASDM file. So after another Google search I found many people with the same issue. The only solution appears to be to downgrade Java&amp;hellip;. but these posts were from  8 years ago&amp;hellip; and that version of Java is long gone&amp;hellip;..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ASA is now basically just a giant piece of e-waste. I did a little bit of searching to see if maybe it was possible to install some sort of alternate firmware on it like OpenWRT, but it would appear that most projects like that don&amp;rsquo;t support Cisco hardware because it is too specialized. So, I guess now I&amp;rsquo;m gonna need to find another firewall to play with&amp;hellip;. looked at some Palo Alto PA-820&amp;rsquo;s on eBay, they don&amp;rsquo;t go eol until 2029, so that&amp;rsquo;s probably a good choice&amp;hellip;. just gonna have to wait until after the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCB Project part 2</title>
      <link>/posts/pcb-project-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pcb-project-part-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;populated-board&#34;&gt;Populated Board&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I populated the board with the Arduino board and the pin headers. Assembly was very straight forward. I added pin headers for the GND and +12V lines for testing purposes, in the future I&amp;rsquo;ll either add a barrel connector or just wire the power supply directly to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251204102135.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-test&#34;&gt;The Test&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.simhubdash.com/&#34;&gt;SimHub&lt;/a&gt; top program the Arduino via USB, connected the fans to the Right and Left fan channels and used a barrel connector that has screw terminals that was able to just slide over the GND/+12V pins.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;populated-board&#34;&gt;Populated Board&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I populated the board with the Arduino board and the pin headers. Assembly was very straight forward. I added pin headers for the GND and +12V lines for testing purposes, in the future I&amp;rsquo;ll either add a barrel connector or just wire the power supply directly to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251204102135.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-test&#34;&gt;The Test&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.simhubdash.com/&#34;&gt;SimHub&lt;/a&gt; top program the Arduino via USB, connected the fans to the Right and Left fan channels and used a barrel connector that has screw terminals that was able to just slide over the GND/+12V pins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251204102149.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the complete setup, fans on either side of the steering wheel are adjustable and can be pointed at the player. The fan setup performed flawlessly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251204102158.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;next-steps&#34;&gt;Next Steps&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I need to add friction fit connectors on the fan headers to ensure they don&amp;rsquo;t accidently disconnect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3D Design/Print a case&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Power connector solution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Underground Wire Locator</title>
      <link>/posts/underground-wire-locator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/underground-wire-locator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;invisible-dog-fence&#34;&gt;Invisible Dog Fence&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While visiting family over Thanksgiving, my dog sitter let me know that an alarm was sounding in my garage. It turns out that alarm was the controller for our invisible dog fence (this is the one we have if you are interested &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/Underground-Electric-Dog-Fence-Premium/dp/B00ZRPGLOC%29&#34;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/Underground-Electric-Dog-Fence-Premium/dp/B00ZRPGLOC)&lt;/a&gt;, stating that there was  break in the wire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A little explanation of how invisible dog fences work, skip ahead to the next paragraph if you are already familiar with the idea&amp;hellip; The controller sends an RF signal down the wire which basically acts like a low power transmit antenna. From the controller, you can increase the RF power on the wire which makes the boundary line &amp;ldquo;thicker&amp;rdquo;, ie more distance on either side of the wire in which the dog will be shocked. The dog wears a collar that acts as a receiver for the signal, if the dog gets too close to the wire and the collar detects the signal, they will receive a shock. There are some additional features like adjustable correction levels, but that&amp;rsquo;s the basic idea of how they work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;invisible-dog-fence&#34;&gt;Invisible Dog Fence&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While visiting family over Thanksgiving, my dog sitter let me know that an alarm was sounding in my garage. It turns out that alarm was the controller for our invisible dog fence (this is the one we have if you are interested &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/Underground-Electric-Dog-Fence-Premium/dp/B00ZRPGLOC%29&#34;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/Underground-Electric-Dog-Fence-Premium/dp/B00ZRPGLOC)&lt;/a&gt;, stating that there was  break in the wire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A little explanation of how invisible dog fences work, skip ahead to the next paragraph if you are already familiar with the idea&amp;hellip; The controller sends an RF signal down the wire which basically acts like a low power transmit antenna. From the controller, you can increase the RF power on the wire which makes the boundary line &amp;ldquo;thicker&amp;rdquo;, ie more distance on either side of the wire in which the dog will be shocked. The dog wears a collar that acts as a receiver for the signal, if the dog gets too close to the wire and the collar detects the signal, they will receive a shock. There are some additional features like adjustable correction levels, but that&amp;rsquo;s the basic idea of how they work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finding a break in a wire that is buried is not generally an easy task, but there is a tool made for this job, the Underground Wire Locator (this is one I purchased for another project that I haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten around to yet  &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B08NPKY94N%29&#34;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B08NPKY94N)&lt;/a&gt;. This works in a very similar way to how the invisible fence works. The locator puts an RF signal on the buried wire and then the user (me) wanders around with a receiver that has an antenna on a weight that hangs near the ground.  By swinging the weighted antenna back and forth like a pendulum you can hone in on the location of the wire by listening to the strength of the tone on the receiver. When the receiver antenna is directly above the buried wire the tone is very weak, but it is strong on either side of the wire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251202145404.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am by no means an RF engineer, but I did stay at a Holiday Inn Express last week in Ohio, and I do have my Extra Class Amateur Radio License (Callsign N8MEM), so I will attempt to explain how this works. The wire in the ground is horizontally polarized while the antenna on the receiver is vertically polarized (this is due to how it is held). When the receiver is directly above the wire the antenna is not receiving the signal at all because it is at a right angle to the direction that the signal is being propagated from the wire in the ground. BUT, if you swing the receiving antenna like a pendulum, as soon as the pendulum passes dead center, the receive angle becomes less than 90 degrees and the receive angle of the antenna intersects with the transmit angle of the wire in the ground. I hope that makes sense, I&amp;rsquo;m sure there are better terms that could be used, but it gets a little out of my area of expertise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was able to find the break in the wire this way, eventually I got to a point in the wire where I no longer had any signal, and I had to dig through 12 inches of snow and some leaves (luckily I live in the woods, and most of the wire was just laid on the ground and has naturally been covered over time). The break was at a splice I had put in the line when I setup the fence, somehow it had come disconnected, not sure what happened, because I didn&amp;rsquo;t actually find the exact spot, I pulled the cable up out of the snow while locating it and suddenly I had the end of the wire. I then had to go back to the transmitter and put it on the other end of the wire and then trace it to where it stopped and dig around in the snow for a bit to find the other end. I twisted them back together with a wire nut and stuck them in a  plastic connector box full of some sort of dielectric grease made for this application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-frequency-does-this-thing-operate-on&#34;&gt;What Frequency Does this Thing Operate On?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is now where things get interesting&amp;hellip;. Curiosity got the best of me, and I started to wonder what frequency this tester is using for it&amp;rsquo;s RF signal. So I went to the manual&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251202153125.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;200kHz, well mystery solved&amp;hellip;.200-275kHz frequencies in the United States are allocated for Aeronautical Radio Navigation and Aeronautical Mobile Radio Use (Check out this awesome chart here&amp;hellip; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ntia.gov/sites/default/files/2025-09/ntia-us-frequency-allocations.pdf&#34;&gt;United States Frequency Allocations &lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wasn&amp;rsquo;t satisfied, I setup my &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sdrplay.com/&#34;&gt;SDRPlay&lt;/a&gt;, Tuned the software to 200kHz and noticed something very interesting when I turned on the transmitter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251202153819.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is actually transmitting on 455kHz. Which is a frequency allocated for Maritime Mobile radio use and Aeronautical Radio Navigation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/455khz%201.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t done much research in to the manufacturer besides trying to visit their website that is on the back page of the manual, http:www.kolsol.net, which conveniently gives a &amp;ldquo;404 Not Found&amp;rdquo; error. Based off the English in the manual I&amp;rsquo;m assuming this was probably a short lived Chinese company&amp;hellip;.The seal of quality on the manual cover tells you everything you need to know&amp;hellip;. &amp;ldquo;Original AUTHENTIC, Patented products, Counterfeiting not allowed.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PWM Wind Simulation PCB Design</title>
      <link>/posts/pwm-wind-simulation-pcb-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pwm-wind-simulation-pcb-design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;problem&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to add Wind simulation to my Sim Racing setup. As you speed up/down you get more/less wind in your face, and you get directional wind in the corners. This helps with immersion by giving a sense of speed. The PC connects to the Arduino which provides the PWM control for the fans, and the fans are then powered by an external 12v power supply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software and hardware designs already exist for this, but they require that you build your own interface using an Arduino.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.simhubdash.com/&#34;&gt;SimHub&lt;/a&gt; is the software that most people use to integrate Arduino microcontrollers with sim racing software titles. SimHub allows you to choose and configure the type of Arduino you would like to use and automatically generates the Arduino Sketch file to interface with the hardware setup. The following image shows the Arduino design for a 2 fan setup using an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/ATmega32U4-Micro-USB-Development-Compatible-ATmega328/dp/B07PHK8SMR&#34;&gt;Arduino ProMicro&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;problem&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to add Wind simulation to my Sim Racing setup. As you speed up/down you get more/less wind in your face, and you get directional wind in the corners. This helps with immersion by giving a sense of speed. The PC connects to the Arduino which provides the PWM control for the fans, and the fans are then powered by an external 12v power supply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software and hardware designs already exist for this, but they require that you build your own interface using an Arduino.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.simhubdash.com/&#34;&gt;SimHub&lt;/a&gt; is the software that most people use to integrate Arduino microcontrollers with sim racing software titles. SimHub allows you to choose and configure the type of Arduino you would like to use and automatically generates the Arduino Sketch file to interface with the hardware setup. The following image shows the Arduino design for a 2 fan setup using an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/ATmega32U4-Micro-USB-Development-Compatible-ATmega328/dp/B07PHK8SMR&#34;&gt;Arduino ProMicro&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251201110508.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;design&#34;&gt;Design&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I implemented this design on some protoboard and got a working protype. The fans used are 12V PC case fans and require their own power supply. In this design, the +12V and GND pins of the fans are connected to an external 12V power supply and the sense pins on the fan are left unconnected, and the PWM pin is connected to the corresponding output on the Arduino.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251201110047.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Prototype worked very well, but was not what I would consider pretty. So I took this as an opportunity to learn how to use some PCB design software. For this project I used &lt;a href=&#34;https://easyeda.com/&#34;&gt;EasyEDA&lt;/a&gt;to design the PCB and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pcbway.com/&#34;&gt;PCBWay&lt;/a&gt;to manufacture the boards. The image below is the schematic design of the board.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251201113215.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the actual board layout with routing complete.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251201113244.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After routing was complete, I exported the Gerber files for the design and submitted them to PCBWay for manufacture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251201110056.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a future post, I will populate the board and test it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>003 - Blog Setup Edits</title>
      <link>/posts/blog-setup-edits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog-setup-edits/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This blog was setup based on instructions provided by #NetworkChuck @ &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dnE7c0ELEH8&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dnE7c0ELEH8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had to made a a few edits to his process/script to make it work for what I wanted to do. He wrote a python script which was intended to transfer images from an #Obsidian vault, but it only accounted for PNG files, I modified the regex to account for JPEG/JPG and GIFs also.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regex edit for image.py&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;        # Step 2: Find all image links in the format ![Image Description](/images/Pasted%20image%20...%20.png)
        #images = re.findall(r&amp;#39;\[\[([^]]*\.png)\]\]&amp;#39;, content)
        images = re.findall(r&amp;#39;\[\[([^]]*\.(?:png|jpg|jpeg|gif))\]\]&amp;#39;, content, re.IGNORECASE) 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;NetworkChuck also didn&amp;rsquo;t explain the process for setting up auto deploy on Hostinger which requires setting up a webhook from Hostinger that is triggered when a post is uploaded to GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;This blog was setup based on instructions provided by #NetworkChuck @ &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dnE7c0ELEH8&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dnE7c0ELEH8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had to made a a few edits to his process/script to make it work for what I wanted to do. He wrote a python script which was intended to transfer images from an #Obsidian vault, but it only accounted for PNG files, I modified the regex to account for JPEG/JPG and GIFs also.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regex edit for image.py&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;        # Step 2: Find all image links in the format ![Image Description](/images/Pasted%20image%20...%20.png)
        #images = re.findall(r&amp;#39;\[\[([^]]*\.png)\]\]&amp;#39;, content)
        images = re.findall(r&amp;#39;\[\[([^]]*\.(?:png|jpg|jpeg|gif))\]\]&amp;#39;, content, re.IGNORECASE) 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;NetworkChuck also didn&amp;rsquo;t explain the process for setting up auto deploy on Hostinger which requires setting up a webhook from Hostinger that is triggered when a post is uploaded to GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>002 - My Second Post</title>
      <link>/posts/my-second-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-second-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;this is another post&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;its-alive&#34;&gt;IT&amp;rsquo;S ALIVE!!!!!!&lt;/h3&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;this is another post&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;its-alive&#34;&gt;IT&amp;rsquo;S ALIVE!!!!!!&lt;/h3&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>001 - First Blog Post</title>
      <link>/posts/first-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/first-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my first blog post&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Hello World!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a jpg&amp;hellip;
!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/581786564_10102380794447054_525479171988765602_n.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a png.
!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251129112637.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;This is my first blog post&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Hello World!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a jpg&amp;hellip;
!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/581786564_10102380794447054_525479171988765602_n.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a png.
!&lt;img src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020251129112637.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/posts/untitled/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/untitled/</guid>
      <description></description>
      <content></content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
